the amount of evidence that is stacking
against Donald Trump is astounding I
keep learning new stuff every single day
Goen Heights has been renamed to Trump
Heights the Goen Heights is
strategically important in the Middle
East that Israel was captured by Syria
during The Six Day War in 1967 and later
annexed in 1981 despite Israel's control
the International Community including
the United Nations has not recognized
Israel's sovereignty over the Gan
Heights
however president Donald Trump made a
historic decision to officially
recognize Israeli sovereignty over Goen
Heights effectively overturning Decades
of US policies that was a bold move so
not only is this a very personal tribute
to Donald Trump but it's very political
all aboard the Trump
train next stop
Donald Trump Light Rail in Jerusalem
which is expected to go to the Temple
Mount is now known as the Trump train
this carries a lot of significant
symbolic meaning especially given the
political and religious context of
Jerusalem and the broader Israeli
Palestine conflict so for those of you
that don't understand the significance
of this this is huge the Temple Mount is
one of the most sacred places in the
entire world because it is revered by
both the Jews
and the
Muslims and any development regarding
the Temple Mount is highly symbolic and
politically charged the light rail is
seen as an effort to make an area more
accessible for Jewish visitors but also
a political statement about Israeli
control and sovereignty over Jerusalem
particularly over the old city and the
Temple
Mount I wholeheartedly think we are
looking at the first beast and for those
of you that are saying that this man is
is not being
worshiped think again definitely seems
like a lot of people are worshiping this
man don't forget that he was also given
a manora of peace and named The Prince
of Peace with an inscription of Isaiah
96 that is supposed to be referencing
Jesus Christ but we all know the
Antichrist is going to take whatever
Jesus did and flip it around he was even
given a crown and apparently the number
one supporter of the Noah hide laws in
US history so I do think World War III
is just around the corner and I believe
a certain someone is going to be the Mr
Fix It to come in and establish peace
but then I predict that this man
will come back to life and the whole
world is going to
go very very soon